http://www.chocovision.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Customer Log-in
(0)Item | Total :
$0.00
Search
x
Login to chocovision
Forgot Password?
Login
Register
x
Please Sign Up It's free and always will be.
By clicking you agree to the Terms and Conditions set out by this site, including our Cookie Use.
Privacy Policy
To our customers,ChocoVision Corp. and ChocoVision.com respect the privacy of our customers. Our Web site is designed to provide you with the highest quality products and customer service. In an effort to accomplish this we record a variety of information from you as you visit our site. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices as well as the options you have in the way your information is collected and used.
Information We Collect:
When you purchase products from Chocovision.com, we collect your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information. This information is used primarily to fulfill your order and to communicate with you about your order. In fulfilling your order, we may share your personal information with outside parties to the extent necessary to fulfill your order. Once you have ordered through ChocoVision.com, we may use this information to:
* automatically place you on our e-mail newsletter list to receive e-mail newsletters with special offers and updates about products and services, unless you reply to ChocoVision with "Remove" in the subject line (located at the bottom of the electronic newsletter).
* automatically place you on our direct mail/catalog list to receive from us direct mail and printed catalogs with special offers and updates about products and services.
Choice Opt-In/Opt-Out:
If you do not wish to receive announcements or special offers from us, you can do the following:
Email Newsletters/Catalogs:If you'd like to be removed from our email list, please reply to ChocoVision with "Remove" in the subject line.
Placing Orders:
If you place an order and want it sent directly to a different recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's name and postal address. We use this information only to ship the product and confirm delivery and do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to fulfill that order. For all International and Canada orders, please contact us 800-324-6252.
Tracking Information:
When you ask that we e-mail you a tracking number for your shipment, we collect your name and e-mail address and use this information to e-mail you tracking information.
Email Questions/Comments:
When you send us an e-mail, we collect your name and e-mail address and use this to reply. We may also place you on our e-mail newsletter list to receive our e-mail newsletters with recipes, special offers, new products and new services. You can unsubscribe from one or more of our e-mail newsletters at any time by replying to ChocoVision with "Remove" in the subject line (located at the bottom of the electronic newsletter).
Data Security:
ChocoVision Corp and ChocoVision.com restricts access to your personal information to those employees who need to know this information to provide services that you request. ChocoVision uses SSL encryption to transmit personal information (such as a credit card number). Although ChocoVision takes strict precautions to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, we cannot guarantee that these precautions will prevent third-parties from illegally accessing this information.
Correction of Information:
We make all reasonable attempts to ensure that the information you submit on this website is accurate and up-to-date. We will take all steps to correct inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information that we are informed about.
Right of Access:
ChocoVision has an area on the site where you can submit feedback.  Any feedback that is submitted through this site becomes the property of ChocoVision. We may use this feedback for marketing purposes or to contact you for further feedback on the site.
Children:
We do not collect information from or about children. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you do not want your child to visit the ChocoVision website, we encourage you to use Web filtering technology to accomplish this.
Privacy Policy Changes:
We reserve the right to change or update this privacy policy at any time at our discretion. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about ChocoVision's commitment to privacy, please feel free to contact us via our website or call us at (845) 473-4970.
HOME
Home
About Us
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Store Policies
TEMPERING MACHINES
Revolation 2
